

Ngo Tan Hung

Back-end Developer

About Me

Hello! I'm **Ngo Tan Hung**. I am passionate about working with computers. I spend hours and hours researching cool stuff on the computer. I love handling user data on a Website or mobile app.

I can easily capitalize on low hanging fruits and quickly maximize timely deliverables for real-time schemas.

Bio

■ DoB

January 2, 1999

☑ Email

ngotanhung02011999@gmail.com

Telegram

username: @HungNgo12345

Phone

(+84)0915625342

Address

1363 Le Van Luong.S, Phuoc Kien.C, Nha Be.D, HCMC

Professional Skills

C#

MASTER

PHP

EXPERT

Framework .NET

ADVANCE

Framework Laravel

ADVANCE

MySQL

BEGINNER

Font-End HTML CSS

GOOD

Font-End JavaScript

GOOD

Font-End React JS

GOOD

Git Github

BASIC

Visual Studio

BASIC

Work Experience



May, 2021 - Present

Leverage agile frameworks to provide a robust synopsis for high level overviews. Iterative approaches to corporate strategy foster collaborative thinking to further the overall value proposition.

Backend Deverloper at Home

June, 2023 - Present

Override the digital divide with additional clickthroughs from DevOps. Nanotechnology immersion along the information highway will close the loop on focusing solely on the bottom line.

Education

O Bachelor of Information Technology from Information Technology Ho Chi Minh City College of Economics

2021 - 2023

References



Vo Van ThuongPresident of Vietnam

Ngo displays exemplary professionalism and is able to take on challenges. He learns quickly and is an asset to any team.



Nguyen Phu Trong General Secretary of the Communist Party of Vietnam

Ngo is a great and problem solver. He is quick to extend his helping hand and makes a good team player.

Contact

(+84)0915625342

☑ ngotanhung02011999@gmail.com